...I pointed out the "check engine" light
to you several months ago.
No, the "check engine" light is fine.
It's still blinking away.
(Penny:)It's the stupid engine
that stopped working.
It cost me, like, $1200 to fix it.
(Sheldon:)You know, it occurs to me. You could solve
all your problems by obtaining more money.
(Penny:)Yes, it occurs to me too.
(Sheldon:)Hang on a moment.
[PENNY GASPS]
(Sheldon:)Here. Take some.
(Sheldon:)Pay me back when you can.
(Penny:)Wow, you got a lot of money in there.
(Sheldon:)That's why it's guarded by snakes.
(Sheldon:)- Take some.
- Don't be silly.
(Sheldon:)I'm never silly.
(Raj:)- Here.
- No, I can't.
- Don't you need money?
- Well, yeah, but...
(Sheldon:)This is money I'm not using.